Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9 Locals, 2.
  - Local 910
    - Local 910 Outgoing Correspondence, March 21, 1939-November 4, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Pickering Telegram to Matles Regarding Holidays and Wages, November 25, 1942; 2.
      - Pickering to James Byrnes Regarding Overtime and Absenteeism, April 28, 1943; 3.
      - Pickering Telegram to Emspak Regarding Dues, May 18, 1943; 4.
      - Pickerings to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Negotiations with March 27, 1946, Pickering Letter to Richard O'Connor, April 1, 1946; 5.
      - Pickerings to Elizabeth Moore Regarding Staff Members, November 4, 1946; 6.
      - George Pio to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues, March 21, 1939; 7.
      - Pio to Emspak Regarding Constitutions, January 6, 1940; 8.
      - Arlene Windell to Matles Regarding Negotiations, February 7, 1942; 9.
      - Windell to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 24, 1942; 10.
      - Windell to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, April 22, 1942; 11.
    - Local 910 Per Capita Reports, January-July 1938 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Local 910 Financial Secretary Report, May-December 1937 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Local 910 Leaflets, October 17, 1946-February 9, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - "Food For Thought" Regarding Wages and Factionalism, October 17, 1946; 1.
      - "Over the Years" Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 9, 1954; 2.
    - Local 910 Organization, April 26-28, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Bertha Owens to Stella, April 26, 1937; 1.
      - Executive Secretary to Owens, April 28, 1937; 2.
    - Local 910 Magnavox Bankruptcy, November 29-December 31, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Bankruptcy Petition, November 29, 1937; 1.
      - James Matles to David Turets, December 22, 1937; 2.
      - Turets to Matles, December 23-27, 1937; 3-4.
      - Matles to Turets, December 29, 1937; 5.
      - Turets to Matles with Newspaper Clippings, December 31, 1937; 6.
    - Local 910 Strike, September 13-15, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - John Gojack Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald, September 13, 1945; 1.
      - Robert Kirkwood to Fitzgerald, September 14, 1945; 2.
      - Gojack to Fitzgerald, September 15, 1945; 3.
    - Local 910 National Labor Relations Board Hearings and Finances, August 3-16, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, August 3, 1954; 1.
      - Gojack to James Matles, August 5, 1954; 2.
      - Matles to Gojack, August 11, 1954; 3.
      - Gojack to Matles, August 16, 1954; 4.
    - Local 910 Correspondence and Wage Rates, February 13, 1941-September 25, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Wage Rates, February 13, 1941; 1.
      - John Gojack to James Matles Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, March 21, 1943; 2.
      - Gojack to Matles Regarding Negotiations, April 12, 1946; 3.
      - Gojack to Matles Regarding Union Ship and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 22, 1950; 4.
      - Staff Memo Regarding Greenville Magnavox and Congress of Industrial Organization Inter-union Rivalry, September 25, 1953; 5.
  - Local 911 (Fort Wayne)
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Officers Lists, July 15, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Outgoing Correspondence, November 2, 1937-April 5, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Robert Henry to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues, November 2, 1937; 1.
      - Henry to Emspak Regarding Disbanding, April 5, 1938; 2.
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937-January 1938 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Financial Secretary Report, May-August 1937 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Per Capita Report, September-December 1937 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Organization, April 30-May 3, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Bertha Owens Telegram to Julius Emspak, April 30, 1937; 1.
      - Executive Secretary to Owens, May 3, 1937; 2.
    - Local 911 (Fort Wayne) Questionnaire and Correspondence, July 1937-April 1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Questionnaire, July 1937; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to James Pascoe Regarding Disbanding, April 20, 1938; 2.
  - Local 911 (Grand Rapids)
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Officers Lists, April 8, 1947-August 18, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Officers Membership, June 12, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Resolution Regarding Civil Rights Congress and Factionalism, June 12, 1947; 1.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Incoming Correspondence, April 24, 1946-November 22, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Local 911 Regarding Membership Meeting, July 7, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Donald Osborn Regarding Unemployment, April 24, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Carlton Sanford Regarding Locals 911 and 914 Amalgamations, December 2, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Sanford to Amalgamation, January 7, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Sanford Regarding Finances, April 22, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Emereno Sciamanna Regarding Factionalism, July 3, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Archie Simons Regarding Per Capita, November 22, 1950; 7.
      - John Gojack to Carlton Sanford Regarding Factionalism and Sanford Trail with March 13, 1947, Richard Wright to Direct Executive Board, March 17, 1947; 8.
      - Gojack to Florence Dutmer Regarding Sanford Expulsion and Factionalism, March 31, 1947; 9.
      - Gojack to Dutmer Regarding Wright Appeal and Factionalism, April 8, 1947; 10.
      - Gojack to Dutmer Regarding Factionalism, April 8, 1947; 11.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Outgoing Correspondence, December 21, 1945-May 1, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Betty Van Bendegar to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, December 21, 1945; 1.
      - Clinton March to John Gojack Regarding Factionalism, December 24, 1947; 2.
      - Donald Osborn to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, April 9, 1946; 3.
      - Carlton Sanford to Emspak Regarding Per Capita Reports and Amalgamations, November 25, 1946; 4.
      - Sanford to Emspak Regarding Amalgamation, December 11, 1946; 5.
      - Sanford to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 17, 1947; 6.
      - Emereno Sciamanna to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, June 22, 1947; 7.
      - Lear Executive Board to Gojack Regarding Disaffiliation, May 1, 1948; 8.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Leaflets, April 11, 1947-August 28, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - "The Only Issue" Regarding Factionalism, April 11, 1947; 1.
      - "We Thought" Regarding Factionalism, August 15, 1948; 2.
      - "An Open Letter" Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, August 28, 1948; 3.
      - "The Strange Case of Richard Wright" Regarding Factionalism, 4.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Pamphlets, December 3, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - PAC Bulletin, December 3, 1947; 1.
      - "There is a Definite Attempt" Regarding Factionalism and Write Appeal, 2.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Lear Avia Organization, April 4-10, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, April 4, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to Gojack, April 15, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Ralph Williams, April 5, 1944; 3.
      - Gojack to Emspak with Newspaper Clippings, April 10, 1944; 4.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Amalgamations, December 6-11, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak, December 6, 1946; 1.
      - Articles of Amalgamation, December 6, 1946; 2.
      - Basil Edge to Emspak, December 11, 1946; 3.
      - John Stoffers to Emspak, December 11, 1946; 4.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Factionalism, January 14-March 13, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to John Gojack with January 7-11, 1947 Richard Wright Letters to Local 911, January 14, 1947; 1.
      - Gojack to Fitzgerald, January 20, 1947; 2.
      - David Mates to Fitzgerald, February 14, 1947; 3.
      - Richard Wright Appeal, March 13, 1947; 4.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Factionalism, February 14, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - John Gojack to Albert Fitzgerald with District 9 Executive Board Report, April 15, 1947, Stanford Expulsion Memo, Newspaper Clippings and Leaflet, February 14, 1947; 1.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Factionalism, April-September 1947 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Owen Smith Memo, April 9, 1947; 1.
      - John Gojack Telegram to Smith, May 22, 1947; 2.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Julius Emspak with May 19, 1947, Carl Sanford Letter to Freeman White, and May 13, 1947, Resolution, June 2, 1947; 3.
      - Richard Wright to James Matles with Investigation Minutes, September 4, 1947; 4.
      - General Executive Board Meeting Investigation Report, September 1947; 5.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Factionalism, November 18, 1947-May 11, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - John Gojack to James Matles with November 5, 1947, David Mates Letter to Gojack, November 18, 1947; 1.
      - Gojack to All Local Unions, November 18, 1947; 2.
      - Gojack Memo to Matles, May 1, 1948; 3.
      - Gojack to Oliver Switzer, May 11, 1948; 4.
    - Local 911 (Grand Rapids) Correspondence, April-December 1947 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Owen Smith to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, April 1947; 1.
      - Elizabeth Moore to UE Locals, December 30, 1947; 2.
  - Local 912 (Fort Wayne)
    - Local 912 (Fort Wayne) Officers Lists, June 21, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Local 912 (Fort Wayne) Outgoing Correspondence, September 1937-March 1938 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Perry Hull to Julius Emspak Regarding UE Convention, September 1937; 1.
      - Hull to Emspak Regarding Officers, April 1938; 2.
      - Evelyn Smith to Emspak Regarding Officers, September 15, 1937; 3.
      - Smith to Emspak Regarding Officers, March 14, 1938; 4.
    - Local 912 (Fort Wayne) Financial Secretary Report, May-August 1937 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Local 912 (Fort Wayne) Per Capita Report, September 1937-July 1938 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Local 912 (Fort Wayne) National Labor Relations Board, August 12-27, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - A. Berry to UE, August 12, 1938; 1.
      - James Matles to Berry, August 27, 1938; 2.
  - Local 912 (Bluffton)
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) Officers Lists, January 5-September 8, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) Outgoing Correspondence, September 1945-April 1947 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Fonda Cook to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Unemployment, September 8, 1945; 1.
      - Edith Barr to UE Regarding Unemployment and Disbanding, April 1947; 2.
      - Anna Garton to UE Regarding Unemployment and Officers, 3.
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) Organization, March 21-30, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, March 21, 1944; 1.
      - Paul Walborn to Emspak, March 27, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Gojack, March 30, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Walborn, March 30, 1944; 4.
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 22-May 20, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - John Gojack to James Matles, January 22, 1947; 1.
      - Matles to Gojack, February 1, 1947; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Gojack with April 1947, Edith Garr Letter to UE, May 12, 1947; 3.
      - Gojack to Emspak, May 20, 1947; 4.
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) Correspondence, November 29, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - John Gojack to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 29, 1946; 1.
    - Local 912 (Bluffton) Leaflets, July 7, 1944-January 27, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Your Case at WLB, July 7, 1944; 1.
      - UE-CIO Negotiating Wage Increase, November 12, 1946; 2.
      - UE-CIO On the Job, December 9, 1946; 3.
      - UE-CIO Fights to Protect You, December 20, 1946; 4.
      - Wage Answer Next Tuesday, January 10, 1947; 5.
      - UE-CIO Reports the Plain Facts, January 27, 1947; 6.
  - Local 912 (LaPorte)
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Officers Lists, October 3, 1950-February 8, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Incoming Correspondence, October 24, 1950-March 21, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Julius Emspak to Vitolius Banis Regarding Organization, October 24, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Dolores Dehne Regarding National Strike Fund, December 18, 1952; 2.
      - James Matles to Dorothy Daniels Regarding Staff Members, March 21, 1952; 3.
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Outgoing Correspondence, October 1950-June 1953 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Dolores Dehne to UE Regarding Plant Closure, June 1953; 1.
      - June Janisch to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 3, 1950; 2.
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Leaflets, January 23, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Union Shop Elections, January 23, 1951; 1.
      - Election Notice, January 23, 1951; 2.
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Newspaper Clippings, November 13-16, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - "Strike at Local Plant Continues", November 13, 1950; 1.
      - "Strike Peace is Far Away", November 16, 1950; 2.
      - "Ray of Hope in Harvell Strike", 3.
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Organization, October 9-24, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, October 9, 1950; 1.
      - Dick Marhanka to Emspak, October 16, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Gojack, October 24, 1950; 3.
      - Emspak to Marhanka, October 24, 1950; 4.
    - Local 912 (LaPorte) Correspondence, January 24, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Dick Marhanka to James Matles Regarding Union Ship, January 24, 1951; 1.
  - Local 913
    - Local 913 Officers Lists, December 6, 1946-December 27, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Local 913 Membership Resolution (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Resolution Regarding Factionalism, 1.
      - Resolution Regarding Officers, 2.
    - Local 913 Incoming Correspondence, January 23, 1945-April 28, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Julius Emspak to Chester Steffen Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 23, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Thomas McGill Regarding Indiana Congress of Industrial Organization, April 28, 1948; 2.
    - Local 913 Outgoing Correspondence, December 30, 1946-March 11, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Thomas McGill to UE Regarding Local Newspaper, December 30, 1946; 1.
      - McGill to Emspak Regarding Indiana Congress of Industrial Organization and Factionalism, April 26, 1948; 2.
      - McGill to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, June 1, 1948; 3.
      - McGill to Emspak Regarding Suspensions and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, July 15, 1952; 4.
      - McGill to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 11, 1953; 5.
      - Chester Steffen to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 11, 1953; 6.
      - Marvin Williams to C. H. Phillips Regarding Factionalism and Officers, July 1952; 7.
    - Local 913 Ledger, 1946-1952 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Local 913 Leaflet (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - "Wage Negotiations To Be Resumed" Leaflet, 1.
    - Local 913 Organization, August 4-28, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak, August 4, 1944; 1.
      - Elizabeth Moore to Emspak, August 18, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Gojack, August 19, 1944; 3.
      - Moore to Emspak, August 26, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Moore, August 28, 1944; 5.
    - Local 913 United Auto Workers-American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, July 11, 1952-March 10, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Johnny Adams to Fellow Workers, July 11, 1952; 1.
      - John Gojack Report Excerpt, July 14, 1952; 2.
      - Charges with July 15, 1952, Thomas McGill Letter, July 14, 1952; 3.
      - McGill to Julius Emspak with July 23-August 13, 1952, Trial Board Minutes, and Expulsion Memo, August 21, 1952; 4.
      - Robert Rice Report Excerpt, November 15, 1952; 5.
      - David Mates to Gojack, February 10, 1953; 6.
      - Rice to James Matles, February 20, 1953; 7.
      - Matles to Rice, February 25, 1953; 8.
      - Rice to Matles, March 10, 1953; 9.
    - Local 913 Correspondence, September 1, 1944-October 9, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Frederick Livingston to Robert Rice Regarding Health Insurance with Health Insurance Rates, September 1, 1944; 1.
      - Rice to James Matles Regarding Dues, and Essex, Ligonier and North Manchester Organizations, October 9, 1946; 2.
  - Local 914 (Fort Wayne)
    - Local 914 (Fort Wayne) Incoming Correspondence, June 29, 1937-April 20, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Julius Emspak to Raymond Thomas Regarding Organization, June 29, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Thomas Regarding Disbanding, April 20, 1938; 2.
    - Local 914 (Fort Wayne) Outgoing Correspondence, June 28, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - Raymond Thomas to E. Bunting Regarding Wages, June 28, 1937; 1.
    - Local 914 (Fort Wayne) Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Local 914 Organization, June 4-11, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Bertha Owens to Julius Emspak, June 4, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Owens, June 8, 1937; 2.
      - Charter Application, June 11, 1937; 3.
    - Local 914 Correspondence, April 20, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Julius Emspak to James Pascoe Regarding Disbanding, April 20, 1938; 1.
  - Local 914 (LaPorte)
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Officers Lists, February 1952-February 1955 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Incoming Correspondence, January 30-March 21, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Julius Emspak to Nettie Schultz Regarding Organization, January 30, 1952; 1.
      - James Matles to Elber Frahm Regarding Staff Members, March 21, 1952; 2.
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Charter Supplies, January 30, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Publications, April 15, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Truth Is Our Weapon, April 15, 1952; 1.
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Organization, January 23-30, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Dick Marhanka to James Matles, January 23, 1952; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Marhanka, January 30, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, January 30, 1952; 3.
    - Local 914 (LaPorte) Strike, May 9-June 13, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak with "Our Welfare is Your Welfare!" Leaflet, May 9, 1952; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Andrew Newhoff, May 9, 1952; 2.
      - Sheehan Letter Excerpt, June 10, 1952; 3.
      - Emma Memo to Janet, June 13, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to William Sheehan, June 13, 1952; 5.
  - Local 914 (Grand Rapids)
    - Local 914 (Grand Rapids) Incoming Correspondence, October 3, 1944-June 27, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Julius Emspak to Antonette Leham Regarding Organization, October 3, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to Frances Charon Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 27, 1945; 2.
    - Local 914 (Grand Rapids) Outgoing Correspondence, September 25, 1944-September 4, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Frances Charon to UE Regarding Veterans and Dues, June 1945; 1.
      - Antoinette Lehman to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, September 25, 1944-September 4, 1945; 2-3.
      - Lehman to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 26, 1944; 4.
    - Local 914 (Grand Rapids) Organization, June 28-August 31, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Barbara Springer to Julius Emspak, June 28, 1944; 1.
      - John Gojack to Emspak, August 28, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Springer, August 29, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Gojack, August 31, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Springer, August 31, 1944; 5.
  - Local 915
    - Local 915 Incoming Correspondence, June 17, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Francis Regarding Organization, June 17, 1937; 1.
    - Local 915 Charter Application, June 10, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Local 915 (Fort Wayne)
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Officers Lists, July 7, 1947-February 10, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Outgoing Correspondence, October 1951 (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - Jack Wasson to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, October 1951; 1.
      - Wasson Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 203 and Factionalism, 2.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Leaflets, October 10, 1946-March 31, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - In Negotiations, October 10, 1946; 1.
      - It Can Be Done Regarding Negotiations, March 10, 1948; 2.
      - Don't Talk Wages Now, March 18, 1948; 3.
      - Company Wants All Profit, March 25, 1948; 4.
      - Union Demands Company Grant Wage Increase, March 29, 1948; 5.
      - Attention Regarding Negotiations, March 31, 1948; 6.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Newspaper Clippings, December 28, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - "Horton Workers To Hold Ballot On Strike Today", December 28, 1949; 1.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Seperate Charter, October-November 1944 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - George Foulk to Julius Emspak, October 1944; 1.
      - Ray Klausner to John Gojack, November 13, 1944; 2.
      - Gojack to Klausner, November 15, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Gojack, November 16, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Elizabeth Moore, November 16, 1944; 5.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Negotiations, April 1947 (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - John Gojack Telegram to James Matles, April 11, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak Telegram to Gojack, April 14, 1947; 2.
      - Gojack to Matles with Contract, April 21, 1947; 3.
      - Wage Rates, April 1947; 4.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Strikes, March 31-April 14, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Al Askenberg to Horton Employees, March 31, 1948; 1.
      - Louis Majors to Albert Fitzgerald with Rates, March 31, 1948; 2.
      - Majors to James Matles, April 7, 1948; 3.
      - John Gojack to Matles with Contract Excerpt, April 14, 1948; 4.
    - Local 915 (Fort Wayne) Correspondence, October 10, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - John Gojack to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 10, 1946; 1.
  - Local 916
    - Local 916 Officers Lists, April 3, 1944-December 18, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Local 916 Incoming Correspondence, February 2, 1938-April 1, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Julius Emspak to Silas Goff Regarding Organization, February 2, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to R. R. Smith Regarding Dies amd Veterans, March 26, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Oscar Rothe Regarding Per Capita, December 26, 1946; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Dorothy Monnier Regarding Newspaper, November 26, 1951; 5.
      - Emspak to Mildred Hall Regarding National Strike Fund, December 18, 1952; 6.
      - Emspak to Ward Fox Regarding Finances, April 29, 1954; 7.
      - Emspak to Fox Regarding Per Capita, May 6, 1954; 8.
      - Emspak to Hall Regarding Finances, June 7, 1954; 9.
      - Basil Pollitt to Dorothy Haywood Regarding Finances, April 1, 1955; 10.
      - David Scribner to Smith Regarding Seniority and Veterans, November 28, 1945; 11.
    - Local 916 Outgoing Correspondence, November 25, 1945-April 26, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Ward Fox to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, March 24, 1954; 1.
      - Silas Goff to UE Regarding Per Capita, January 26, 1938; 2.
      - Mildred Hall to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 4, 1954; 3.
      - Dorothy Mennier to Emspak Regarding Lockouts, November 24, 1951; 4.
      - Dorothy Harwood to Emspak Regarding Finances and Lawsuit, April 26, 1955; 5.
      - O. C. Rothe to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 19, 1946; 6.
      - Rothe to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Dues, December 20, 1946; 7.
      - Rothe to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, September 23-December 3, 1947; 8-9.
      - Alice Simison to UE Regarding 1948 UE Convention, July 22, 1948; 10.
      - R. R. Smith to Emspak Regarding Seniority to Unemployment and Veterans, November 25, 1945; 11.
      - Berverly Spiegel to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 1, 1946; 12.
    - Local 916 Correspondence and Contributions, December 3, 1947-April 1, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - Political Action Committee Contributions, December 3, 1947; 1.
      - Memo Regarding Legal Expenses, March 26, 1955; 2.
      - Basil Pollit to Mary Whitehead with Bill, April 1, 1955; 3.
    - Local 916 Leaflet, May 29, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - "UE Wins" Leaflet Regarding IUE and United Auto Workers-American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, May 29, 1952; 1.